madcowmodels.com 2011-11-22

# MadcowModels | The Free Online Networking Website for the Modeling and Photographic Industry

**Effective date: 1st February 2010.**

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Madcow Models ("us", "we") and its website, http://www.madcowmodels.co.uk ("the Site", "the Service"), uses and protects any information that you give Madcow Models when you use this website.   
Privacy Policy Summary: 

• We will not collect personally identifying information about you through the Site unless you disclose such information to us;   
• We will not knowingly disclose personally identifying about you that we collect through the Service to third parties.   
• We will take reasonable steps to protect the security of the PII we collect from you through the Service.   
Madcow Models may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

**1\. Information you give us**

 _a. The type of information Madcow Models collects._

We collect any information you enter on the site or give us any other way, such as through emails, surveys or letters.   
The information we collect varies on how you use the site. Our registration process requires you to enter your email address, name, age and that you are able to legally work in the United Kingdom ("UK").   
You may enter other information into the Site by going to the update profile, or similar, sections on the website. 

_b. Information publicly available on the site._

Please be aware that information you voluntarily provide information to public areas to the site, such as your profile or forums, the information will be available for others to see and possible use. We therefore recommend you do not disclose personally identifying information such as email address, postcode, address, workplace or instant messenger address in public areas of the site. We are not responsible for any personally identifying information you voluntarily submit to publicly accessible places. We may highlight publicly available information you submit to the site, such as forum posts and comments and reviews, on the front page of the site. 

**2\. Automatic Information Collection**

 _a. Cookies._

Like a lot of websites, the site, utilizes cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. We use cookies to link to remember your information and link certain activities to you. It is possible to block, or limit, the cookies any website sends to your computer and you can do so by following the relevant instructions for your browser. If you do turn off cookies, the site may not function as Madcow Models intends it. Its design and appearance also may not be as Madcow Models intends it to be. Our cookies do not collect the personally identify information that you supply to us during the application process. Our cookies do collect the following information 

i. The date and time you visited the site.  
ii. Your computers IP address, its operating system, platform, whether javascript is allowed and browser type & version number.  
iii. Your demographic and other non personally identifying information.  
iv. Information to combat misuse and fraud.  
v. The host you use to connect to the internet, and from which website you direct-linked to ours from.  

_b. Contests, sweepstakes and promotions._

From time to time we may run a promotion, contest or sweepstake. Your may be asked to voluntarily provide personal information, or voluntarily provide it to a third party in connection with the contest, sweepstake or promotion. It will be disclosed at the point of information collection or transfer who is collecting the information you supply and whose privacy statement will apply. It will then be your choice as to whether you want to or not to supply this information to a third party or us. 

**3\. What we do with the information you give us.**

 _a. Use of Personally Identifying Information._

We use your personally identifying information for purposes such as responding to your requests, maintaining your Madcowmodels.co.uk account, Monitoring and providing the service, enforcing our rights and the rights of any third parties and ensuring compliance with the terms and conditions of the site. We may use your Personally Identifying Information to contact you, for reasons such as to inform you that you have a new message from another member, to inform you of deletions of your posts or threads from the forum or any other content you post. We may also email Madcowmodels.co.uk newsletters or any other similar communications about the site and us. 

_b.Opting Out._

Subject to the exceptions outlined below, you may modify your settings to change the type of communication you receive from the site and us. We will also outline details on promotional and marketing emails how to unsubscribe or contact us to inform us of your preferences regarding receiving promotional or marketing emails from us and the site. We reserve the right to send you business communications such as thread or post deletion notices, removal or banning of your account notices, address confirmations and transaction information regarding your account with the site. We may not offer you a choice to opt out of these communications during the time you are registered with the site. 

_c.Usage of non-Personally Identifying Information._

We use non-personally identifying information about users and visitors for purposes such as measuring the amount of traffic on the site, making the service more useful to its users and also to monitor the levels of usage on certain functions of the service to determine its popularity. We use IP-addresses to analyze trends on the site, track a users movement on the site, administer the site and gather information on the site demographic for non-personally identifiable use only. 

_d.Retention and storage of non-Personally Identifying Information._

We retain non-personally identifying information as long as required, allowed or we deem it useful. We do not undertake any retention obligations and therefore we may dispose of non-personally identifying information without notice, subject to applicable law. 

**4\. Sharing of Information.**

 _a. Advertisers and Others._

We may share non-publicly identifying information with advertisers, service providers and other persons or businesses with whom we conduct business. These advertisers, services providers or other persons and businesses may share non-personally identifying information about you with us and the site that they have independently gathered and collected. 

_b. Business Transfers._

As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses and their assets. We may also engage in acquisitions, mergers, changes of control, restructurings or other similar moves and transactions. Customer Information is generally one of the transferred business assets and your personally identifying information may be subject to such transfer. In the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, your information may be transferred to a debtor or bankruptcy trustee in possession and then to a subsequent buyer. 

_c.Compliance and safety._

We may release user and customer information when we believe is appropriate. Such as: 

i. Make disclosures under programs intended to prevent potential crimes or investigate persons.  
ii. Enforce or apply agreements, including the terms and conditions of the site.   
iii. Protect the rights, property, the users, of others and the site http://www.madcowmodels.co.uk including exchanging information with companies for fraud protection or credit risk reduction.  
iv. Comply with applicable law, and respond to legal process including search warrants and court orders. Or respond to written complaints of copyright infringement.  

**5\. Information Security.**

 _a. Your Obligations._

You must protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Please sign off when you are done using the site. Your emails are not neccisarily secure from interception so do not include sensitive information in them. We generally do not ask for passwords via email. If you receive an email requesting your password please be vigilant and use the online contact form to contact us directly. 

_b. Our Security Measures._

We take reasonable precautions to protect the security of users information. We have electronic, physical and managerial processes and procedures in place to help safegaurd and protect your personal information. However, neither people nor security systems, even encrypted systems, are foolproof. In addition to this people may make mistakes, not follow procedure or people may commit intentional crimes therefore whilst we use reasonable efforts to secure your personally identifiable information, we can not guaruntee its absolute security. If applicable law imposes any non-disclaimable duty to protect your personally identifiable information, you agree that intentional misconduct will be the standards used to measure our compliance with that duty. 

**6\. Website Links.**

The site may link to other websites, these links may be placed by the site staff or by users. We are not responsible for the content of these websites nor are we responsible for their privacy policies. This privacy policy applies only to the information collected by the site. 

**7\. Conditions of use.**

 _a. Revisions._

We reserve the right to change our policy at any time. Clarifications and non-material changes will take effect immediately. If we make non-material changes, we will indicate at the top of this page the revised policy's new effective date. If we make material changes, we will notify you by email or through a notice on the home page of the site and will also indicate so at the top of this page. The material changes will take effect 30 days after such notice. We encourage you to take note of the privacy policy every 30 days to check for material changes to the policy. 

_b. Privacy Concerns._

Your use of the service and any dispute over privacy is subject to the terms and conditions. If you have a concern about privacy on the site please contact us with a thorough description at emails@madcowmodels.co.uk and we will try to resolve it. 

_c. Identity theft._

If you believe you are a victim of identity theft you are entitled by law to request information from us. Write to us using the email address above and we will contact you with the information you must provide to us. After we have receieved this information, we will at no charge release the information we are required to give to you, subject to law and reserving all our rights and defenses. 

_d. Notice required by law._

If we are required to disclose to provide notice of invasion of certain security systems, we will do so by email to the most recent email address you have provided. It is critical you keep your contact and email information up to date and correct at all times. 

©Copyright 2011 Madcow Models.   
All Rights Reserved. Any photos contained on this page are copyright of their respective owners. All Rights Reserved. All Trademarks are the property of their respective owners.
